more than what's up yeah
fluoride forward is a toxic is a toxic
industrial by-product and the men that
handle the fluoride barrels are wearing
full hazmat gear until they pour it into
the pipe that feeds the city and then
everything's fine fluoride is also how
the Gurkha was how a handful of German
soldiers maybe 10 or 13 German soldiers
could keep a thousand people in a prison
camp completely calm and relaxed and
just assure them towards the gas
chambers because they've been giving
them so much fluoride think the people
couldn't you know rise up so so back to
step off the pedestal about soap box now
the DC power DC power going in here any
type you want to play with and it
doesn't matter which panel which is
positive which is negative in this
condition no it does and I set this up
to be positive in this up to be negative
and I've got my negative pole in the
center and my positive on the edges and
that's all it only matters if you're
going to be in an area where you could
brush up where where the edge of your
machine could brush up against the
ground so let's say you were building
something like this and you're putting
it into a car you'd want to position
your positive and your negative so that
it didn't so they couldn't brush so that
your positive could not brush up against
the frame of your vehicle so that's the
only that's the only criteria but that's
more of a installation concern rather
than a design concerns I like this way
it's personal preference but I like how
this generates gas there are subtle
differences and but that takes it takes
like about a year of working with the
gas to to start see the subtle
differences
people resonate with different setups so
this is the way I like is there any
entrainment or not that's not the word
I'm looking for conditioning
conditioning involved in this involved
with this
there's conditioning with this and this
is a conditioning process and I can
describe that real quick conditioning
the plates in a system like this you
power it with a little bit over current
a little bit a little bit more energy
than you would normally power and you
cannot power with pulsed DC with you
condition the plates by running them
with with a whole lot of sodium
hydroxide and some gold and some
electrodes on my electric water and you
you let the water run you let the water
boil away don't replenish it you let it
all run out what that does is it puts a
nice layer of you can't see it on these
but it puts a nice conditioning layer on
the plate and then you do it again layer
of layer of a catalyst put a nice
condition layer of catalyst essentially
what you're doing is you're you're
conditioning the first first molecule
the first atoms of the of each plate
you're conditioning them with with a
material that's going to encourage the
production of hydrogen it's going to
take it to the point of separation and
their electricity pushes it over so
that's that's what we're going on here I
know your system or be able to the place
you have tells but for that's what
that's how you conditioned this that's
this that's a secret okay actually
sounded place first right what's up his
son the place first do you send the
plates I do Sam the plate actually I
don't stand the plates anymore let me
show
but I do I like anodized aluminum you're
creating a hard surface for different
surveys on Mackenzie yeah let me tell
you that go real quick here what I just
described was letting the water run out
letting the water run out during the
conditioning process instead of instead
of replenishing it and keeping it full
that is something that took me a lot of
years to learn because I would condition
and take me it'd take me a week to can
properly condition a plate the protocols
are on actually there on PES wiki right
now in a lot of ball voices work so but
when I when I learned that if you let it
let the water level drop over as its as
its running and then when you fill it
back up it's going to condition it's
going to run even better
but that's only with that's only with my
gold catalyst that's not with regular
sodium hydroxide follow the normal
conditioning procedures that Bob laid
out with sodium hydroxide and you'll be
you'll be fine but anyway what I do now
instead of sanding because I've been
working in production levels I have to I
have to find the fastest way to do this
so I was working when I was doing these
I was running about three minutes of
proper sanding and conditioning or
proper sanding and prepping of each
plate okay and that was just way too
slow when you're doing in a hundred and
twenty plate system or something like
that just makes way too long so what I
actually found was that if I took a wire
brush I don't know if you can see that
on camera okay you can took a wire brush
I'll just show look better on the camera
than it does really oh nice I took a
wire brush on my drill motor just and
what's interesting is this is like it
looks very similar to the tree or the
Flower of Life diagrams they found in
Egypt so I really like this way of
conditioning the plates and I do that to
all my plates that just and I could do a
plate in about 20-30 seconds completely
completely scratched or
prepped for for the box so and then I
just like this I just like the type and
I like the pattern so much I did all my
ends with it too
so anyway you can even see it on that
one there just for aesthetics yes this
is what we call a dry cell the water is
only inside and inside the inside the
circle okay so you see the circle that I
remember yeah so we're gonna put water
in here there's little holes drilled in
the bottom of the plates and that's what
communicates the water to the center and
then the hydrogen is generated comes out
the holes in the top and escapes there
we can see what we call it dry cell when
you say hydrogen you're talking ahead by
two oxygens Browns gas whatever you want
to call it there's this there's a
there's a conflict between the brown
ziens and the road Ian's and they
they're saying no we should be called
Browns gas no they should be called
roads gasps no they should be called
they're super gas now and what not roads
pioneered the work started it out much
as much as you see me doing this here
Rao excuse me
Brown took the work and quantified it
there's I there's actually things that I
can't say about Brown and his work with
the hydrogen because it's not mine to
give away it's something somebody else
fit it to me under under confidentiality
but let me just say that what I talked
about in my lecture about water about
the different parts of water is so
important for proper Browns gas research
that there are different parts of water
if you distill a quart if you distill a
gallon jug into four quarts every court
will have its own characteristics and
you want to use certain courts you
actually want to use the first two
chords that come off in the last two for
an alchemist or what we call fixed you
don't want to use the last two quarts
you want to use the first two quarts
here's the last two quarts for water
plants or something to give a plug
surely you say to get on the water do
you just do it I'm gonna night and you
get it from an ice-cream and it's dead
what do you mean by distilling okay
before we answer that question boy oh
can you pause for a second please just
to give a plug for where people can get
those DVDs of your presentation go to
Tesla tech info and those will be
available shortly where you can purchase
those DVD of your presentation and I
would recommend doing it was a
fascinating presentation you gave
yesterday I'm really excited because
this is the first time in three years
that they've actually for the last was
yeah it was the last three years
somehow the copy of my of my lecture
that was destroyed either the sound was
completely garbled it was unintelligible
or the or the video just didn't show up
I find that very ironic very interesting
so if they've already produced it this
one they know as a matter of fact they
set up a special camera in there it was
completely independent of everything
else a backboard it just to make certain
that they that everything worked out
okay your question is how do you distill
water you could distill what you can get
out there's a stainless steel distill it
well plastic shell on the outside
stainless steel on the inside you can
distill water any type of water but if
you were distilled reverse osmosis water
it'll be much cleaner on your on your
distillery unit so you just pour the
water in it distills off and like I said
for Browns gas work you want to take the
first two corpse that come off okay
Brown had a little bit different way of
separating his water which like I said I
can't talk about it because I have to
honor my you know my friend of Silas no
I have to under my
you know the confidentiality so anyway
so the first two quarts of water what
you want to use in all these systems the
other courts you want to add to your add
to your Gardens or wonder your plants
with or because they're what an
alchemist would call fixed they're
harder to separate the first two are
very volatile and they are they're much
more attuned to what we have here so
that said and so you're using the first
two quarts coming from the distiller to
run in this process yes uh-huh and so
you actually for this process you could
throw in spring water and that's good I
mean you would think well you're gonna
use the first two but what you're saying
is don't use the third fourth and fifth
in your in your batch that goes on the
garden only use the first two and if you
want to make six quarts you know you're
gonna have to do this three times to get
the first two quarts so would you say
that this alchemical process you've
discovered is that that's a crucial
component or something that is a make or
break this this will work without it
okay I'm in Alzheimer's you can just use
distilled water you just use whatever
your whatever you want to in this one
you can throw in spring water you can
throw in salt so ocean water if you're
if you're really adventurous but what I
found to make really good gas and to
have really dynamic and powerful effects
if you use the the the first two quarts
of water the first two sections of water
you will find a more
you'll find a more powerful gas you'll
find it seperates more easily that type
of thing so it's a preference not a
requirement someday it may be a
preference because I'll tell you what
how many people are actually not
something it may be a requirement not a
preference because how many people are
remediating nuclear waste like Brown's
death all right is there anybody people
have tried it and they can't do it but
if you use this other system you can
because Brown did not talk about where
he was getting his water okay Brown did
not talk about the type of water he was
using that was his secret so let's get
back into the procedure of us running
this thing we've talked about the
preparation of the water we talked about
the hooking up of the DC what are the
considerations is there a pump involved
in running those voltages you want to
run if you set it up the way I've done
it you run you run a 12 volt solar panel
no no panels or troubles they're
actually like 8 or 16 and that's fine
just if you're running this like this
over here you're going to you're going
to daisy chain your solar panels
together and generate 120 volts and put
it into it but for this one a 12 volt
this design that I've created here a 12
volt solar panel I'm not really
concerned about the amperage it'll take
as much as it wants and your panel and
and just have at it so 12 volts or 18
volts or whatever it's called if you
don't get up to 20 volts because that's
weight or 2824 excuse me a 24 volt panel
just stick with the regular panels that
you can use to charge batteries an RV
solar panel or a couple of them work
together that's fine so or a DC power
supply a lot of generators have DC power
supplies now you just hook up
click-click from the from the generator
and the way you go now a lay person how
much are you filling this all the way to
the top with water well
how are you teleported see my see my a
little line there I'm not filling it all
the way up I'm not filling it up to
these electrodes basically I just
measured how much water was going to
fill in here I figured about a gallon
and a half and a gal and a half it's a
little bit high next time I'll use about
a gallon and a quarter so that the
waters below the plates but it doesn't
really matter as long as you're not
filling it all the way up and you know
allowing this electrode to to interact
with that electrode because then you're
going to lose a lot of your power here
and you want to focus your power here
well then this involved with this
there's conditioning with this and this
is a conditioning process and I can
describe that real quick
conditioning the plates in a system like
this you power it with a little bit over
current a little bit a little bit more
energy than you would normally power and
you cannot power with pulsed DC if you
condition the plates by running them
with with a whole lot of sodium
hydroxide and some gold grooves and
that's the only that's the only criteria
but that's more of a installation
concern rather than a design concerns I
like this way it's personal preference
but I like how this generates gas there
are subtle differences but that takes it
takes like the about a year of working
with the gas to to start see the subtle
differences and different people
resonate with different setups so this
is the way I like is there any
entrainment or not that's not the word
I'm looking for conditioning
conditioning in German soldiers could
keep a thousand people in a prison camp
completely calm and relaxed and just
assure them towards the gas chambers
because they've been giving them so much
floor I think the people couldn't you
know rise up so so back to step off the
pedestal though its soapbox now the DC
power DC power going in here anytime you
want to play
and it doesn't matter which panel which
is positive which is negative in this
condition no it doesn't I set this up to
be positive yeah fluoride forward is a
toxic is a toxic industrial by-product
and the men that handle the fluoride
barrels are wearing full hazmat gear
until they pour it into the pipe that
feeds the city and then everything's
fine fluoride is also how the dirt
moves' how a handful of German soldiers
maybe 10 or 13 us up to be negative and
I've got my negative pole in the center
and my positive on the edges and that's
all the other it only matters if you're
going to be in an area where you could
brush up where where the edge of your
machine could brush up against the
ground so let's say you were building
something like this and you're putting
it into a car you'd want to position
your positive and your negative so that
it didn't so they couldn't brush so that
your positive could not brush up against
the frame of your vehicle